<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<hunt id="bath-easy">
	<number_of_clues>22</number_of_clues>
	<circular>Y</circular>
	
	<outcome type="elimination">
		<blurb>Identify the odd one out from this list</blurb>
		<answer_list>
			<option id="dickens">Charles Dickens (1812-1870)</option>
			<option id="john">John Wood the Elder (1704-1754)</option>
			<option id="linley">Thomas Linley (1733-1795)</option>
			<option id="herschel">William Herschel (1738-1822)</option>
			<option id="nelson">Horatio Nelson (1758-1805)</option>
			<option id="pitman">Isaac Pitman (1813-1897)</option>
			<option id="gainsborough">Thomas Gainsborough (1727-1788)</option>
			<option id="alfred">Queen Anne (1665-1714)</option>
			<option id="malthus">Thomas Robert Malthus (1766-1834)</option>
			<option id="fielding">Henry Fielding (1707-1754)</option>
			<option id="austen">Jane Austen (1775-1817)</option>
			<option id="lawrence">Thomas Lawrence (1769-1830)</option>
			<option id="oliver">William Oliver (1695-1764)</option>
			<option id="shelley">Mary Shelley (1797-1851)</option>
			<option id="pitt">William Pitt the Younger (1759-1806)</option>
			<option id="palmer">John Palmer (1742–1818) </option>
			<option id="elizabeth">Queen Elizabeth I (1533-1603)</option>
			<option id="louis">Louis XVIII (1755-1824)</option>
			<option id="scott">George Gilbert Scott (1811-1878)</option>
			<option id="siddons">Sarah Siddons (1755-1831)</option>
			<option id=""></option>
		</answer_list>
	</outcome>
	
	<clues>
		<clue number="1">
			<output>
				<direction>Start in front of Bath Abbey facing the doors, in the pedestrianised area.</direction>
				<question>How many angels are climbing Jacob's ladder on the abbey (watch out for fallen angels!)? Remove the person listed at this number from the list.</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>10</answer>
			<result>dickens</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="2">
			<output>
				<direction>Turn your back to the abbey and pass between ionic columns into Stall Street.  Turn left, then right into Bath Street. With the small Cross Bath in front of you, turn left into Hot Bath Street, then right into Hetling Court.</direction>
				<question>Which saint is associated with the hospital?  Cross off the architect with the same first name.</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>St John</answer>
			<result>john</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="3">
			<output>
				<direction>At the end of the passage turn right into Westgate Buildings.  Follow this road straight on, past the various side-turnings around Sevendials and up the hill.</direction>
				<question>Whose bust is this?</question>
				<image>Royal Theatre Shield</image>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>David Garrick</answer>
			<result>linley</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="4">
			<output>
				<direction>Continue straight on into Barton Street until you reach Queen Square.</direction>
				<question>When was the obelisk erected?  Cross of the person who was born in that year.</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>1738</answer>
			<result>herschel</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="5">
			<output>
				<direction>Walk around the square to the opposite corner, and take the road into Queens Parade</direction>
				<question>What kind of animal guards the gate to Royal Victoria Park?  Remove the person with all the letters in their name.</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Lion</answer>
			<result>nelson</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="6">
			<output>
				<direction>Walk up the nearby set of steps into Gravel Walk.</direction>
				<direction>At a junction of paths turn right and walk up to Brock Street.  Turn left into the Royal Crescent.</direction>
				<question>Someone on your list used to live here.  You can remove them from the list.</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Isaac Pitman</answer>
			<result>pitman</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="7">
			<output>
				<direction>Return to Brock Street and walk along the road to King's Circus.</direction>
				<question>Who lived in a house with these carvings above the door?  Remove this person from the list</question>
				<image>Carvings</image>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Thomas Gainsborough</answer>
			<result>gainsborough</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="8">
			<output>
				<direction>Leave the Circus by Bennett Street and turn right in front of the Assembly Rooms onto a footpath.</direction>
				<question>Whose bust is this?  Remove from your list the person sharing the same initial and rank.</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Alfred</answer>
			<result>alfred</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="9">
			<output>
				<direction>Follow the footpath to the bottom. Turn left into St Andrews Terrace, then right into Bartlett Street.  Emerge onto George Street.</direction>
				<question>There is one stone lady amongst a row of stone men.  What number is she from the left?  Remove the person listed at this number.</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>4</answer>
			<result>malthus</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="10">
			<output>
				<direction>Turn right, and stay on the high pavement.</direction>
				<question>Two brothers put their stamp here.  Cross off the person who shares the elder brother's first name</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Henry Stafford Smith</answer>
			<result>fielding</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="11">
			<output>
				<direction>Turn left into Gay Street.</direction>
				<question>Who is celebrated in a house on this street?  They died at the same age as the number of the house.  Remove them from the list</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Jane Austen</answer>
			<result>austen</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="12">
			<output>
				<direction>Turn left into Old King Street, follow it around to the right, then continue straight on under the arch.  Carry straight on along a little road called Trim Bridge and then turn left onto Upper Borough Walls.</direction>
				<question>What is the name of the hospital founded in 1738? It seems to suggest that Evian can cure all ills!  Cross off your list a name that includes the first letter of all four words in this building's name.</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Royal Mineral Water Hospital</answer>
			<result>lawrence</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="13">
			<output>
				<direction>Turn left into Old Bond Street, which will take you onto Milsom Street – the main shopping road.  A little way up Milsom Street you can turn right into Green Street.  Follow it to the end.</direction>
				<question>Whose profile is depicted above a door?  Remove this person from the list</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Dr Oliver</answer>
			<result>oliver</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="14">
			<output>
				<direction>Turn left into Broad Street.</direction>
				<question>Who designed the school?  Remove the person whose surname rhyme with his surname!</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Thomas Jelly</answer>
			<result>shelley</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="15">
			<output>
				<direction>Continue up Broad Street, looking out for Broad Street Place, an alleyway on the right.  Take it.</direction>
				<question>Who designed this water feature?  Remove the person with a very similar name</question>
				<image>Floating globe</image>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>William Pye</answer>
			<result>pitt</result>
		</clue>
		<clue number="16">
			<output>
				<direction>Follow the steps down into Walcot Street (if steps are a problem, retrace your steps and go down Saracen Street onto Walcot Street instead.  Turn right on Walcot Street and go straight on.</direction>
				<question>This decoration adorns which building?  Cross off the person whose invention benefited this establishment.</question>
				<image>PostOffice</image>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Post office</answer>
			<result>palmer</result>
		</clue>		
		<clue number="17">
			<output>
				<direction>Next, turn left into Bridge Street.</direction>
				<question>Whose statue was erected here on the year of their death? This person lived here in their youth but you are looking for their predecessor by 300 years</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Victoria</answer>
			<result>elizabeth</result>
		</clue>		
		<clue number="18">
			<output>
				<direction>Continue straight on.  Although there are shops on either side, you are actually walking across Pulteney Bridge.  There are only two other bridges in the world with shops on both sides.  After the bridge continue on until you find a traditional old pharmacy.</direction>
				<question>When was the chemist established?  Cross off the person who had already died by this year</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>1826</answer>
			<result>louis</result>
		</clue>		
		<clue number="19">
			<output>
				<direction>Now retrace your steps, but look out for an illusory window.</direction>
				<image>FakeWindow</image>
				<question>Who owned a bookstore and lending library here?  Cross off the person with the same initials</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>George Gregory</answer>
			<result>scott</result>
		</clue>		
		<clue number="20">
			<output>
				<direction>Return across Pulteney Bridge, and turn left into Grand Parade.  Walk along by the river and then beside the gardens.  When you reach the junction with North Parade, turn right and cross the road then go straight on into North Parade Passage, tucked away in the corner.</direction>
				<question>Who lived here in 1680, in what is reputedly the oldest house in Bath?  Remove the person whose first name starts with the same letter</question>
			</output>
			<hint></hint>
			<answer>Sally Lunn</answer>
			<result>siddons</result>
		</clue>
		<after>
			<output>
				<direction>At the end of the alley, turn right and you should find the abbey ahead of you again.  Well done!</direction>
			</output>
		</clue>
	</clues>
</hunt>