<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<location id="richmond">
	<name>Richmond-upon-Thames</name>
	<title>Richmond-upon-Thames Treasure Hunt</title>
	<images>
		<image>img/places/RichmondMain.JPG</image>
	</images>
	<map>
		<coord></coord>
	</map>
	<tab type="image" name="photo">
		<label>Image</label>
	</tab>
	<tab type="text" name="intro">
		<label>Summary</label>
		<content>
<![CDATA[
Richmond is a splendid town on the banks of the River Thames to the west of London. Once home to kings and queens as the site of Richmond Palace, this is still a prosperous area.  With a handsome high street, a beautiful riverside, plenty of green spaces and stunning views from Richmond Hill it's easy to see why. So why not let us show you the best little corners of Richmond-upon-Thames with a Treasure Hunt?
]]>
		</content>
	</tab>	
	<tab type="text" name="details">
		<label>Hunt Info</label>
		<content>
<![CDATA[
<b>Hunts</b> The pack includes a treasure trail and a bonus round.
<br/><br/>
<b>Duration</b> 2 hours or so, not including breaks.
<br/><br/>
<b>Suitability</b> Suitable for any size of group from 1 to 8, good for families. The streets of Richmond are accessible to all, and any steps can be detoured around. 
<br/><br/>
<b>Requirements</b> Just a pencil and paper, and a sensible pair of shoes.
]]>
		</content>
	</tab>
	<tab type="text" name="todo">
		<label>Things to do</label>
		<content>
<![CDATA[
<ul>
<li>It's only a ten minute walk from Richmond train station to <a target="_blank" href="http://www.kew.org/">Kew Gardens</a>, an amazing place to visit at any time of year whether you are a keen gardener or not</li>
<li><a target="_blank" href="http://www.royalparks.org.uk/parks/richmond-park">Richmond Park</a> is unique, there's nowhere else in London where you can walk for hours and fool yourself into thinking you're in rolling countryside miles from anywhere</li>
<li>The <a target="_blank" href="http://www.petershamnurseries.com/">Petersham Nurseries</a> is what anyone would think of if them picture an idyllic English garden nursery. It has a lovely cafe and restaurant too, though you must book for lunch</li>
</ul>
]]>
		</content>
	</tab>
</location>
